I love
waffles ego
waffles you get them in the freezer you
put them in the toaster
delicious and all my
life I've watched the commercials for
the Eggo
waffles it's always the same setup
right
it's two
[Music]
children but just one waffle that's
right and then the
children
fight for the
waffle
y'all those waffles come in a box of
10 I've done the research I've logged
the
data and I feel like we can all
agree everyone in this room no matter
where you're from no matter what you
believe no matter who you voted for we
can all
[Music]
agree that
waffles
are to be eaten two at a flipping
time so if we
fighting over one
waffle that means one of you little
skinny girls just ain't
one or Worse one of you fat boys had
three
now I have to start my morning with
violence because you couldn't commit to
number
[Laughter]
four I shouldn't even really be eating
waffles I have the
gird the acid
reflux yeah see some of you
nodding some of you little young skinny
girls just don't know what I'm talking
about I'mma explain it to you I'm
explain it to you so you know what's
what's
coming um one
day you're going to be
asleep in
bed
asleep
and
fire is going to Surge from your belly
up into the back of your throat jolting
you out of bed making you wonder what is
[Music]
this and you're going to remember that
you ate a piece of pizza three days
ago and the tomatoes are now attacking
your
system
I had to go to the doctor I made an
appointment to get seen about this
luckily it's a very easy fix you just
take a little pill take a little pill
and I'm right back on the
sauce marinara that's
right but my doctor explained to me that
it might also be soothing to my stomach
if I were to eat a banana every
day
now I'm sure you can tell by this
haircut I'm not a lady who really enjoys
[Applause]
bananas now I will eat them but I like
to cut them up into little pieces stab
them with a toothpick and have them like
that
and the real reason I don't care for
bananas is because they attract
flies I hate flies I don't use that word
very often but I hate flies I hate them
so much that I ordered an electric
tennis
racket and I am the Wimbledon champion
of the world at my house
o I love to just sneak into the kitchen
early in the morning right you flip on
the lights real fast and then
just I like it when a big fly comes
through the window I call those
juicers cuz they'll stick to the
electric grid for just a minute and
Sizzle y'all there is nothing like to
smell a burnt fly in the
morning
delicious so I don't keep bananas in my
house what I do to get my banana is I
walk down to the little Fruit Stand in
my neighborhood I buy a banana I eat it
on my way home I throw the peel into a
neighbor's trash
can that way I don't have to deal with
it it's the kind of citizen I
am
so the other morning I I get to the
Fruit Stand and the little fellow who
works there same little fella every
morning he looks at me and he says why
you are always buying only one banana
you could buy two three whole bunch of
bananas you could sleep late in the
morning you were always only buying one
banana at the time so I felt
triggered
attacked but I did think to myself you
know I would like to sleep later in the
mornings maybe I'll buy two bananas
today eat one on the way home and then
just save one for tomorrow and then I
can sleep in and still have my banana
what can happen in one
night so I buy two bananas I walk home I
eat one banana on the way throwing the
peel into a neighbor's trash can to be
neighborly and when I get home I'm just
holding a banana in my hand and when I
open the door to my apartment my little
cleaning lady is there sweetest little
Guatemalan lady I love her but we don't
speak the same language quite literally
it's a lot of pointing and drawing
pictures it's it's very difficult and
she sees me holding just a banana and
she's looking at me and she's looking at
the banana and she's looking at me and
she's looking at the banana so I thought
that this would be funny I
went
hello it's for
[Laughter]
you
hola she was very upset to find out it
was indeed just a
banana she started to say bad words to
me in Spanish I don't know what Gordo
means but I think it's
I think it's pretty I think that's what
it
is so I'm excited that I have a banana
for the next morning the next morning I
sleep in I wake up I flip the lights on
in the kitchen and there is my
banana surrounded by fruit
flies what's going on here this banana
is still sealed by the Lord I don't
understand how fruit flies are already
around this
banana so I tell you what I did I ate
that banana fast I took the peel I put
it in the trash bag I tied it off and
I'm taking this trash bag directly down
to the trash these flies are not getting
another chance in my house not
today so I have to head down to the back
alley that's where the trash is in my
building I go down the back steps I open
the gate I put the bin open I put the
bag into the bin and as I'm closed
closing the bin lid I realized there are
funsize candy bars strewn about the
alley like scattered all over the ground
you know what I'm talking about those
little fun like you get them at
Halloween little 100 Grand little butter
fingers little Nestle crunches and at
first I thought somebody was trying to
lure me
somewhere then I realized that there was
no pattern to the
scatter and I'm just I I can't imagine
what happened why would why would the
alley be filled with just C and
look I wanted
them I wanted them but I'm an adult I
don't know if I'm allowed to eat candy
off the ground in the alley is that
allowed can we do that it wasn't open or
anything
right so I'm having this moral dilemma
do I do I eat these candy bars or not
because let's be real if these were
full-size candy bars I'd already be up
in my apartment enjoying them I am only
having this moral crisis because I'm
like is it worth all the
bending right it's very upsetting so I
didn't know what to do and uh I'm
standing there contemplating how I'm
going to proceed when my neighbor walks
up this judgy cow she
gets right up on the situation she's
like Jennifer what are you
doing I'm
like do you not see the delicious candy
all over the ground oh you can't eat
that were you going to eat that yeah I
was thinking about
it oh Jennifer you can't eat that it
could be laced with
drugs I didn't even think of
that now I really want
it
[Applause]
I just spent 2 years alone in my
apartment some drug laced alley candy
sounds real good right
now a lot of
fun I left it there I didn't take it but
if that candy is still there when I get
home tomorrow it's mine that's just
that's just the
rules and my roommate doesn't get it she
doesn't get it at all she's skinny
mhm
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and I don't look I don't want to
disparage her for being healthy that's
probably a good thing but you know she's
just her name is
Sarah doesn't that just sound like a
little bunny fart
Sarah all the time cold I have never met
a human being all all the time Co you
could take this girl to the sun she's
going to bring a hoodie I'm telling you
she's cold all the time she came up to
me last week she was like Jennifer I
know it's hot outside but
um I'm
freezing do you think just for a minute
we could just turn the air conditioner
off I said let me explain this to
you I weigh 300 lb it's 108° outside you
could roast a chicken between my bosom
don't touch
it that is not a good time to catch me
if I am hot or hungry you need to keep a
safe distance okay if mama needs a
biscuit you don't want to risk it that's
how it
goes and I hope you didn't get offended
by that
that's little string ban of a thing you
just cuz the truth is that it doesn't
matter what I say somebody could get
offended right I could say I could tell
a joke about Walmart and one of y'all be
like that's not funny my mama was killed
by Fallen
prices it's why that smiley face wears a
hard hat cuz of my
mama I didn't
know I do love uh traveling I get to
travel a lot with this job I just got
back from my hometown I was down in uh
Louisiana you got
any that's no it's fine that's how I
feel about it too just kind
of difficult Hard Times we're living I
love going to Louisiana though y'all cuz
I stay with my nana when I'm down there
I love my nana y'all she is 88 years old
the coolest lady I have ever met I love
hanging out with her and the reason it's
so much fun to hang out with her now is
cuz about 10 10 years ago when my paaw
died she took all the money he left her
and she started pimping out her house
right like making her crib nice she has
a bad back so she put a a big old hot
tub on a deck right there in the yard uh
she does have any of her real teeth left
uh so her refrigerator's always full of
pudding
cups thank you Nana and
uh and she has the biggest TV I've ever
seen I'm not kidding y'all they gave
this old woman one inch TV for every
year she's been alive it's huge it's
really
big and if she is awake the TV is on and
she keeps the TV tuned to the Game Show
Network and her favorite show is Family
Feud y'all we watched it every day I was
there and I'm not kidding you we were up
late one afternoon it was like
3:30 and we could not take our our eyes
off this particular episode y'all cuz
the families were tied the families were
tied the point value is tripled top
three answers are on the board name
something you put on a baked potato my
nana stands up and screams aluminum
[Applause]
fo she's not wrong she's not wrong
but when the number one answer was
butter po she's
mad when answers two and three were sour
cream and chives she lost it right there
in the living room she stood up I have
been making baked potatoes since
1952 I've made him without butter I've
made him without sour cream I'm not
entirely sure what the heck of child
even
is but I had never in my life made a
baked potato without the aliminum foil
and then she just got up and turned the
TV off and went to bed she was done with
all of
us she doesn't like my phone my cell
phone CU it makes too many noises right
she calls it my Bing
Bong she's like Jennifer your Bing Bong
is Bing Bong and come get your Bing
Bong she doesn't even know what it's
called but she wants to know who it is
right what why is it bing bonging it's
just an email Nana who's it
from um The Electric Company what are
they
saying well I owe him
$183
so I might just stay here for an extra
couple days if that's
okay the best part about staying at
Nana's houses come 6:
p.m. I got the whole place to myself
right she takes a pill at 5:30 and goes
night night I'm in the hot tub with a
pudding cup like I love Nana this is
delicious I almost got I almost got in
trouble though cuz she she said to me
she said what is it you do when I go to
bed I mean I'm not going to lie to my
nana so I was like
wellow I've been eating copious amounts
of pudding in the hot
tub she's like oh
baby that's not good for you that heat
and all that
milk I said well I'm not doing that
tonight Nana it's my last night here and
tonight I just see that they're running
a marathon of this TV show I've been
wanting to see so I'm going to get some
pudding cups and sit in front of the TV
and just watch watch my show and she
says well it's your last night here so I
tell you what
tonight I'm not going to take my pill
I'm going to stay up and watch t TV with
you a't that
sweet I was like
wow what are you going to do with that
pill so we got some pudding
cups we sat in front of the TV now the
TV show I was dying to see at the time
was the people versus OJ Simpson right
that was a very big deal when I was a
young kid I mean we've never seen
reality TV at that point you know what I
mean that was crazy for us we were
getting to look at our first
Kardashian right we didn't know what
that was going to turn into did we
nobody nobody could have foreseen that
it was crazy and I loved it I was so
addicted to it when it was happening in
real life and so I really wanted to see
this you know reenactment of it and
after about three episodes I realized
that Nana does not remember that this
happened the first
time cuz she says to me after episode
three she
goes you know
what I bet you that Mark Ferman guy
turns out to be
racist I was like I think you're
right and I saw an
opportunity so I bet my nana $183 that
they find OJ not
guilty she took that bet and that's how
I paid my electric bill that's
right
[Applause]
don't get upset she's my nana she'd want
me to have lights it's
[Applause]
okay I love going home too because I get
to see my
nieces so sweet and they love my cell
phone they love my cell phone because
they use it as a camera they love to
take pictures of every themselves
everything they they just got a pet
rabbit for Easter I don't know if y'all
uh understand how many pictures of this
rabbit we need but it's a lot it's a lot
of pictures of the and they figured out
that the camera you know you can flip it
to take a picture of the the rabbit and
then they flip it back to take a picture
of them picture of the rabbit picture of
them picture of the rabbit and if they
start that back and forth with the
camera going too fast it freezes up and
the little one got mad she was like a
Jen it's not
working I was like Miss
ma'am do you know when I had to go
through at your age to take a
picture it was a lot of Click crank
crank crank click crank crank like 30
something times you didn't know what you
had a p you didn't get to see it right
away you sent that away for a week a
week you could have had 32 pictures of
your finger you didn't
know and then finally after years of
that they came out with 1 hour
processing remember oh you're only going
to have to wait 1 hour for your pictures
tell me to wait an hour now for my
pictures I will beat you like biscuit
dough on Sunday don't you even try that
with
[Applause]
me I have a real weakness when it comes
to trying to be healthy it's um it's
Girl Scout
cookies I love I love Girl Scout cook
and look my my my little nieces were
selling the Girl Scout cookies this year
there are 17 different kinds of Girl
Scout cookies today do you know that
when I was a kid there were
four four two syllables
four there was the lurad dun right a
shortbread cookie I don't know who Laura
dun was but the woman made a delicious
cookie there was the uh peanut butter
Tagalog is what it's called it's a
peanut butter on top of that shortbread
cookie dunked in chocolate thank
you breakfast of
champions there's the thin
mint yes which I think we can all agree
is to be eaten straight out of the
freezer and you know what you we have
skinny girls to thank for that yes
here's what happened a skinny girl
bought a box of thin mints and she was
like I'll never be able to eat all these
at
[Applause]
once how will I keep them
fresh and then her skinny mama was like
put him in the freezer and then her fat
friend came over and was like don't you
have anything to eat in this
house she pulled the cookies from the
freezer the fat girl ate them and was
happy and shared it with the world so
you're welcome you're
[Applause]
welcome but the champion Girl Scout
cookie the best one of them all is the
Samoa named that because after you eat a
box you want Samoa of
them it's a shortbread cookie shaped
like a ring with toasted coconut and
caramel on top drizzled and chocolate to
be put on your finger like a ring and
eaten into a smaller
ring what I like to do is put one on
each finger and eat them in Rapid
succession and whichever finger finishes
first gets another
[Applause]
cookie that's the way to do
it the problem is every time I eat Girl
Scout cookies I want to drink coffee and
and and the gird just the acid I can't
do coffee I mean there's not enough
bananas in the world for me to have a
cup of
coffee so but I but I still I digress
sometimes and I buy the coffee thinking
like it's going to be fine so I was
walking home from the coffee shop with
my coffee and before I had even taken a
sip I'm like uh I don't want to drink
it's going to make me I'm going to feel
so terrible all day but I already bought
it's a $5 C what am I what do I do here
and then I see a homeless fella right in
front of my house and I was like oh this
is perfect I'll give him my coffee I
won't feel bad we'll have a little
moment this will be great so I go up to
the spell and I'm like hey man this is a
brand new coffee I promise I haven't had
one single sip of it would you like it
it's a latte vanilla delicious and he
was like oh thanks thanks and he took
the cup of coffee and we sat there and
we had a little conversation we were
high-fiving laughing I was telling him
about my girls got cookie trying out
material on them you know that's that's
what I like to do and um um and he says
to me th this was really nice thank you
so much I mean I I just have to say
thank you for seeing me people pass by
me all day long and nobody nobody ever
even looks at me and you stopped and
talked to me and and you gave me this
this coffee it was so kind of you you
know I think I have enough change for a
couple of donuts do you want to walk and
go get some donuts with me and I was
like oh man that's that's so sweet so
kind but
I don't want you to spend your money on
me
besides there's a whole bunch of free
candy bars in this alley right
here let's do
this thank y'all so
much thank
you